<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Media on Crypto Chasers Confidential</title>
    <link>https://cryptochasers.net/categories/media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Media on Crypto Chasers Confidential</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2018 C.C.C.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 16:27:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cryptochasers.net/categories/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FUD Alert: Be on the lookout for false news on China</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-china-02072018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 16:27:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-china-02072018/</guid>
      <description>Be wary of misleading articles regarding China&amp;rsquo;s ban of foreign exchanges. While it is true that China has banned foreign exchanges there has not been any official mention that China is banning mining or cryptocurrency completely. Secondly, China FUD has been coming and going since the very early days of cryptocurrency although it is important - the crypto market % in China is not what it used to be. Japan which used to be a much smaller market is now much larger than China when it comes to crypto and lots of positive news is coming from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUD Alert: Mainstream media back at it again</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-02072018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 16:15:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-02072018/</guid>
      <description>Mainstream media is at it again as well as many other news outlets spreading fud - after taking a slight break attacking cryptocurrencies on Tuesday - news outlets such as CNBC are releasing headlines such as, &amp;ldquo;Most cryptocurrencies will crash to zero, Goldman Sachs says&amp;rdquo; other recent articles point out the recent hacks of Ethereum and how &amp;ldquo;devs don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do&amp;rdquo; also releasing articles like &amp;ldquo;This NFL player lost money in Bitcoin and now he is listening to Warren Buffett&amp;rdquo; despite the recent price rises there will always be FUD being released - although not all of it is FUD, there are certainly many more positive articles popping up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>