<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Crypto Chasers Confidential</title>
    <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Crypto Chasers Confidential</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2018 C.C.C.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 13:54:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cryptochasers.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Binance Issues Resolved: Data backup restored, system updated</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/binance-issues-resolved-02092018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 13:54:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/binance-issues-resolved-02092018/</guid>
      <description>After the closure of Binance the spread of FUD was rampant up to a point where John McAfee was in an all out Twitter war with the CEO of Binance Changpeng Zhao (CZ). The issues were resolved on 10am UTC time on February 9th. After the trading went live web traffic on Binance increased substantially and the site is currently experiencing constant denial of service attacks due to the combination of high traffic as well as malicious players running their own denial of service attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litecoin Update: Multiple payment processors, growing lightning network nodes, Litecoin Core 0.15.1rc1</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/litecoin-update-02082018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 22:35:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/litecoin-update-02082018/</guid>
      <description>This week marks a very positive week as multiple payment processors have announced support for Litecoin. There is much interest in the LitePay payment platform similar to BitPay but without the 5% fees. LitePay is expected to launch on February 26th, 2018.
Aliant Payments the most recent to add Litecoin to their payment processor is a large credit card processing &amp;amp; merchant services provider - it is one of the first to cryptocurrency solutions (BTC, LTC, ETH) for merchants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Informative Guide to Cryptocurrency Scams</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/informative-guide-to-scams-02082018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 15:30:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/informative-guide-to-scams-02082018/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t really have a post regarding scams without first including the infamous Carlos Matos of Bitconnect. Later in the post we&amp;rsquo;ll briefly get into the rise and fall of Bitconnect and what it exactly is, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure most of you have already seen this clip but here it is in all of its glory - the notorious Carlos Matos at the Bitconnect Annual Ceremony:
  Lending Cryptocurrency Scams a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View All of Our Released Documents</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/view-docs-02072018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 17:18:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/view-docs-02072018/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to easily view all of our documents please check out our Documents Page which has all of our documents in the categories of:
 Coins : In depth free high quality fundamental analysis of coins. Events : In depth analysis of a significant cryptocurreny related event. FUD Reports : FUD reports which are a digest of all of the FUD released on that particular day, we release these if there is a notable FUD-fueled day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scam Alert: Impersonating crypto accounts and fake donation scams</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/scam-alert-02072018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 16:31:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/scam-alert-02072018/</guid>
      <description>Watch out for social media accounts that ask for donations as part of fake promotions by posing as prominent figures in the crypto space Watch out for false posts on Reddit saying that wallets or exchanges are shutting down and they need donations, we pointed out one on the Electrum wallet Reddit page the other day Note: We will never shill any referral links on this channel nor will we ever ask for donations, if you see anyone posing as us - DM us on Twitter and let us know!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUD Alert: Be on the lookout for false news on China</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-china-02072018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 16:27:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-china-02072018/</guid>
      <description>Be wary of misleading articles regarding China&amp;rsquo;s ban of foreign exchanges. While it is true that China has banned foreign exchanges there has not been any official mention that China is banning mining or cryptocurrency completely. Secondly, China FUD has been coming and going since the very early days of cryptocurrency although it is important - the crypto market % in China is not what it used to be. Japan which used to be a much smaller market is now much larger than China when it comes to crypto and lots of positive news is coming from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUD Alert: Mainstream media back at it again</title>
      <link>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-02072018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 16:15:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cryptochasers.net/posts/fud-alert-02072018/</guid>
      <description>Mainstream media is at it again as well as many other news outlets spreading fud - after taking a slight break attacking cryptocurrencies on Tuesday - news outlets such as CNBC are releasing headlines such as, &amp;ldquo;Most cryptocurrencies will crash to zero, Goldman Sachs says&amp;rdquo; other recent articles point out the recent hacks of Ethereum and how &amp;ldquo;devs don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do&amp;rdquo; also releasing articles like &amp;ldquo;This NFL player lost money in Bitcoin and now he is listening to Warren Buffett&amp;rdquo; despite the recent price rises there will always be FUD being released - although not all of it is FUD, there are certainly many more positive articles popping up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>